Hello, everyone, and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Catherine.
我是Catherine。
And sometimes you're just tired of work, you're tired of everything, you want to go somewhere
有时候你厌倦了工作，厌倦了一切，想去某个地方
for a nice romantic weekend, you take a holiday or a getaway.
度过一个浪漫的周末，休假或短途旅行。
That's right.
没错。
So why don't we take a look at this word on Vocabulary Preview.
那我们来看看词汇预览中的这个词吧。
Vocabulary Preview.
词汇预览。
Okay, so Marco, the word I mentioned is getaway.
好的，Marco，我提到的词是getaway。
It has a couple of different meanings in English.
它在英语里有几种不同的意思。
What are we talking about today?
我们今天要讲什么？
Well, to get away from someone would be to like leave, right, to try and stay far away.
嗯，to get away from someone意思是离开，对吧，试图保持距离。
But a getaway, so taking it as a noun, a romantic getaway, is actually to take a holiday or
但getaway作为名词，比如浪漫短途旅行，实际上是指休假或
romantic escape from the city, escape from your daily normal life.
浪漫逃离城市，逃离日常的平凡生活。
That's right.
没错。
So it's usually kind of brief or sudden, almost like you're just going to sneak out and then
所以它通常比较短暂或突然，就像你偷偷溜出去，
come back in a couple of days.
过几天再回来。
Exactly.
正是。
So many people refer to them as island getaways if you go to an island or a romantic getaway
所以很多人称之为海岛短途旅行，如果你去海岛，或者浪漫短途旅行，
if you have a romantic two-day vacation or something like this.
如果你有两天的浪漫假期之类的。
Right.
对。
And what are you getting away from?
那你是在逃离什么？
You're getting away from work, you're getting away from the busyness of the city, you're
你在逃离工作，逃离城市的繁忙，
getting away from noise.
逃离噪音。
It's a nice way to get into the countryside or as you said, the islands.
这是一种去乡村或像你说的去海岛的好方式。
Exactly.
正是。
So I think we can take a look at our dialogue.
所以我觉得我们可以看看对话了。
We actually were going to a travel agency called Getaway Tours and we're going to try
我们实际上要去一家叫“完美短途旅行”的旅行社，
and see if we can book a nice romantic getaway.
看看能不能订到一个浪漫的短途旅行。
Welcome to Perfect Getaway Tours.
欢迎来到完美短途旅行旅行社。
How can I help you?
有什么可以帮您的？
I would like to plan a surprise getaway for me and my wife.
我想为我和妻子计划一个惊喜短途旅行。
Very well.
很好。
We have a couple of different options such as beaches, the wilderness, the countryside
我们有几种不同的选择，比如海滩、荒野、乡村，
or even going to a spa for the weekend.
甚至周末去水疗中心。
I think something in the countryside would be nice.
我觉得乡村的某个地方不错。
Perfect.
完美。
This package includes round trip flights to New Hampshire.
这个套餐包括往返新罕布什尔州的航班。
A free airport pickup is included.
包含免费机场接送。
Our VIP limousine will pick you up and provide you with complimentary champagne and finger
我们的VIP豪华轿车会来接您，并提供免费香槟和小吃，
foods to soften this 30 minute ride to the countryside.
让这30分钟的车程到乡村更舒适。
Sounds good.
听起来不错。
What is the hotel that we'll be staying at like?
我们要住的酒店是什么样的？
That is the best part.
这是最棒的部分。
Your hotel is actually an old country villa that has been restored and refurbished to
您的酒店实际上是一座古老的乡村别墅，经过修复和翻新，
accommodate a maximum of 10 guests.
最多可容纳10位客人。
You will enjoy an intimate and private time in this very spacious and warm hotel.
您将在这个非常宽敞温馨的酒店里享受私密时光。
Included in the price is three meals a day, excluding beverages.
价格包含一日三餐，不包括饮料。
You can choose to eat at the fabulous restaurant that offers a stunning view of the lush green
您可以选择在绝佳的餐厅用餐，那里可以欣赏到郁郁葱葱的绿色花园的壮丽景色。
garden.
Or if you prefer, your own private butler can arrange your meal to be served in your
或者如果您愿意，您的私人管家可以安排您的餐食送到您的房间
room or outside on our terrace.
或外面的露台上。
Wow this sounds like something my wife would really enjoy.
哇，这听起来像是我妻子会非常喜欢的东西。
Are there any outdoor activities we can take part in?
有什么户外活动可以参加吗？
Of course.
当然。
The hotel has a stable with beautiful stallions for a very romantic horseback ride along the
酒店有一个马厩，里面有漂亮的骏马，可以沿着乡村小径
country trail.
进行非常浪漫的骑马之旅。
You can also go fishing at the nearby lake or visit the local vineyard.
您还可以在附近的湖边钓鱼，或者参观当地的葡萄园。
I'm sold.
我动心了。
I want to book this trip.
我想预订这次旅行。
I don't care what it costs.
我不在乎花多少钱。
Money is no object.
钱不是问题。
Alright we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So I think this sounds pretty romantic right?
所以我觉得这听起来很浪漫，对吧？
It sounds too good to be true.
听起来好得令人难以置信。
It's perfect.
太完美了。
They have butlers and food and horseback riding.
他们有管家、食物和骑马。
That's right.
没错。
So she actually mentioned a couple of interesting words there describing where they're going
所以她刚才提到了一些有趣的词，描述了他们会去哪里
to go or how they're going to spend their time.
或者如何度过时间。
So why don't we take a look at those now on Language Takeaway.
那我们来看看语言要点中的这些词吧。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
Okay so the first word has to do with where this couple is going.
好的，第一个词和这对夫妇要去的地方有关。
They're going to the countryside.
他们要去乡村。
That's right the countryside.
没错，乡村。
So what exactly is the countryside?
那么乡村到底是什么？
Well countryside or the country is the opposite of the city.
嗯，乡村或乡下是城市的对立面。
So it's anywhere that is rural or less developed than a city.
所以它是任何农村或不如城市发达的地方。
Not big skyscrapers or businesses or big towns.
没有高大的摩天大楼、商业区或大城镇。
It's actually pretty quiet.
实际上非常安静。
Okay so usually the countryside will have a lot of natural wildlife.
好的，所以通常乡村会有很多自然野生动植物。
Trees, gardens or farms I think can be considered part of the countryside.
树木、花园或农场，我觉得都可以算是乡村的一部分。
And so yeah that's basically the complete opposite from a city right?
所以，没错，这基本上和城市完全相反，对吧？
Yes and that's why a lot of people take getaways to the countryside because it's as far away
是的，这就是为什么很多人会去乡村度假，因为它离城市越远越好。
from the city as you can go.
离城市越远越好。
Okay very good and to get to the countryside they're actually taking a round trip flight
好的，很好，而要去乡村，他们实际上要乘坐往返航班。
to New Hampshire.
去新罕布什尔州。
Alright so round trip is an important vocabulary item when we're talking about travel because
好的，所以“往返”是谈论旅行时的一个重要词汇，因为。
you can use this for train tickets, flight tickets, even boat tickets.
你可以用它来形容火车票、机票，甚至船票。
It means that you're going there and you're coming back.
意思是你去那里然后回来。
It's basically two tickets.
基本上就是两张票。
Right so the opposite would be if you buy a one-way ticket or a one-way flight.
对，所以相反的情况是，如果你买一张单程票或单程航班。
That's right so many people dream of buying a one-way ticket to the island.
没错，所以很多人梦想买一张去岛上的单程票。
They never have to come back but round trip means you're going to come home at some point.
他们永远不用回来，但“往返”意味着你最终会回家。
So they're actually going round trip to New Hampshire and also they're getting picked
所以他们实际上是往返去新罕布什尔州，而且还会有人接机。
up at the airport where they're going to have a nice limo that's going to offer them complimentary
在机场接他们，那里会有一辆豪华轿车，提供免费香槟和小吃。
champagne and finger foods.
免费香槟和小吃。
Okay my favorite kind of champagne.
好的，我最喜欢的那种香槟。
Complimentary.
免费赠送的。
That's right this means that they're not going to pay for it right?
没错，这意味着他们不用付钱，对吧？
It's free.
是免费的。
So the company is going to pay for it.
所以公司会付钱。
You can have complimentary food, you can have complimentary service.
你可以有免费的食物，也可以有免费的服务。
These are basically things that someone else is providing for you.
这些基本上都是别人为你提供的东西。
You don't have to pay for them.
你不需要为它们付钱。
Even on talking about flights sometimes people will get a complimentary upgrade to first
甚至在谈论航班时，有时人们会得到免费升舱到头等舱。
class that means they are getting a better service for free.
这意味着他们免费获得了更好的服务。
Not me.
我可没有。
Hey if you work for an airline I would love complimentary bump to first class.
嘿，如果你在航空公司工作，我很乐意免费升到头等舱。
And what about this finger foods?
那这个“finger foods”呢？
What about that?
那个是什么？
That sounds kind of strange.
听起来有点奇怪。
Yeah it might sound disgusting but it's not actually fingers that you eat.
是啊，可能听起来有点恶心，但并不是真的吃手指。
It's food that you can eat with your fingers.
是可以用手拿着吃的食物。
So they're like small little treats or snacks that you can have.
所以就是一些小点心或零食，你可以拿着吃。
Exactly usually if you go to a cocktail party or if you go to a party at a museum or an
没错，通常如果你去鸡尾酒会，或者去博物馆或活动派对。
event they'll have these little little foods that you can pick up and eat.
他们会有这些小食物，你可以拿起来吃。
You don't need a fork or a spoon.
不需要叉子或勺子。
Okay so they're very small convenient little snacks that you can just kind of pick at and
好的，所以它们是非常小巧方便的小零食，你可以随便拿。
pop into your mouth.
然后放进嘴里。
All right and all of this they're doing because they have a 30 minute ride to the countryside
好的，他们做这一切，是因为他们有30分钟的车程去乡村。
so they want to soften the 30 minute ride.
所以他们想缓和一下这30分钟的车程。
Okay so to soften something means to make it more enjoyable or more pleasurable.
好的，所以“soften”某物意味着让它更愉快或更舒适。
Because oh no the 30 minute ride is so rough so hard.
因为，哦不，30分钟的车程太辛苦了，太难熬了。
And so boring.
而且太无聊了。
So this makes it better.
所以这让它变得更好。
Okay so yeah you can soften things such as the ride to the countryside or you can even
好的，所以你可以缓和一些事情，比如去乡村的车程，或者你甚至可以。
soften someone up so maybe give them some nice compliments so they'll be nice to you.
先讨好某人，比如给他们一些好听的赞美，这样他们就会对你好。
That's right to soften.
没错，就是“soften”。
Okay all right so why don't we take a break and listen to the dialogue again and we'll
好的，那我们休息一下，再听一遍对话。
be back with language takeaway part two.
然后我们会回来继续语言要点第二部分。
Welcome to Perfect Getaway Tours.
欢迎来到完美度假之旅。
How can I help you?
有什么可以帮您的吗？
I would like to plan a surprise getaway for me and my wife.
我想为我和妻子计划一个惊喜度假。
Very well.
很好。
We have a couple of different options such as beaches, the wilderness, the countryside
我们有几种不同的选择，比如海滩、荒野、乡村。
or even going to a spa for the weekend.
或者甚至去水疗中心度周末。
I think something in the countryside would be nice.
我觉得乡村的某个地方会不错。
Perfect.
完美。
This package includes round trip flights to New Hampshire.
这个套餐包括去新罕布什尔州的往返航班。
A free airport pickup is included.
包含免费机场接送。
Our VIP limousine will pick you up and provide you with complimentary champagne and finger
我们的VIP豪华轿车会接您，并提供免费香槟和小吃。
foods to soften this 30 minute ride to the countryside.
来缓和这30分钟去乡村的车程。
Sounds good.
听起来不错。
What is the hotel that we'll be staying at like?
我们要住的酒店是什么样的？
That is the best part.
那是最好的部分。
Your hotel is actually an old country villa that has been restored and refurbished to
您的酒店实际上是一座古老的乡村别墅，已经修复和翻新过。
accommodate a maximum of 10 guests.
最多可容纳10位客人。
You will enjoy an intimate and private time in this very spacious and warm hotel.
您将在这个非常宽敞温馨的酒店里享受私密时光。
Included in the price is three meals a day excluding beverages.
价格包含一日三餐，不包括饮料。
You can choose to eat at the fabulous restaurant that offers a stunning view of the lush green
您可以选择在绝妙的餐厅用餐，那里可以欣赏到郁郁葱葱的绿色花园的壮丽景色。
gardens or if you prefer, your own private butler can arrange your meal to be served
或者如果您愿意，您的私人管家可以安排您的餐食。
in your room or outside on our terrace.
送到您的房间或外面的露台上。
Wow, this sounds like something my wife would really enjoy.
哇，这听起来像是我妻子会非常喜欢的东西。
Are there any outdoor activities we can take part in?
有什么户外活动我们可以参加吗？
Of course.
当然有。
The hotel has a stable with beautiful stallions for a very romantic horseback ride along the
酒店有一个马厩，里面有漂亮的骏马，可以沿着乡村小径进行非常浪漫的骑马之旅。
country trail.
沿着乡村小径。
You can also go fishing at the nearby lake or visit the local vineyard.
您还可以在附近的湖边钓鱼，或者参观当地的葡萄园。
I'm sold.
我买了。
I want to book this trip.
我想预订这次旅行。
I don't care what it costs.
我不在乎花多少钱。
Money is no object.
钱不是问题。
Alright, we're back and now we're going to take a look at a good group of adjectives
好了，我们回来了，现在我们要看看一组很好的形容词。
that the travel agent used to describe how great this hotel is, how great the place is.
这些是旅行社用来描述这家酒店有多棒、这个地方有多好的形容词。
Language takeaway.
语言要点。
Okay, so the person on the telephone representing the travel company is trying to sell something.
好的，电话里代表旅游公司的那个人正在推销东西。
So she's using these really, really great adjectives to make everything sound awesome.
所以她用了这些非常非常好的形容词，让一切听起来都很棒。
And one of the first things she says is that you will enjoy an intimate and private time
她说的第一件事就是，你将在这家很棒的酒店里享受一段亲密而私密的时光。
in this great hotel.
在这家很棒的酒店里。
Okay, so an intimate time, if something is intimate, it means it's very, I don't know,
好的，亲密时光，如果某件事是亲密的，那意味着它非常，我不知道，
it usually means like romantic, right?
通常意味着浪漫，对吧？
Romantic, cozy, but also private.
浪漫、舒适，但也私密。
So something that is intimate is usually between two people.
所以亲密的事情通常发生在两个人之间。
Okay, so if they're going to have an intimate and private room, that means it's a room only
好的，所以如果他们有一个亲密而私密的房间，那意味着这个房间只属于他们。
for them.
只属于他们。
Yes, or if someone has an intimate relationship, that means that they're romantically involved.
是的，或者如果某人有亲密关系，那意味着他们有浪漫关系。
Okay, and the travel agent went on to describe how fabulous the restaurant is.
好的，旅行社接着描述了这家餐厅有多棒。
So this adjective is really nice, fabulous.
所以这个形容词非常好，棒极了。
I think you have to say it like that, fabulous.
我觉得你得这么说，棒极了。
So this means that it's just a wonderful restaurant.
所以这意味着它只是一家很棒的餐厅。
And some people even say totally fab.
有些人甚至说“超棒”。
Okay.
好的。
Can you describe someone as fabulous?
你能用“棒极了”来形容一个人吗？
Not really, right?
不太行，对吧？
He is so fabulous.
他太棒了。
She is fabulous.
她太棒了。
Really?
真的吗？
You can say that?
可以这么说吗？
My mom says it all the time.
我妈妈经常这么说。
Yeah, so it also depends on, I think, your personality.
是的，所以这也取决于，我觉得，你的个性。
This is a very, very descriptive word.
这是一个非常非常描述性的词。
So sometimes it's a bit too strong.
所以有时候有点太强烈了。
You have to be careful.
你得小心点。
But yeah, you can describe a person, you can describe a place, you can describe a thing
但是是的，你可以用“棒极了”这个词来形容一个人、一个地方或一个东西。
with the word fabulous.
用“棒极了”这个词。
All right.
好的。
Apart from having this fabulous restaurant, they also have a stunning view of the gardens.
除了有这个棒极了的餐厅，他们还有花园的绝美景色。
All right, stunning is similar to the word breathtaking or shocking in a good way.
好的，“绝美”类似于“令人屏息”或“惊艳”，是好的方面。
It makes you really, really impressed because it's so beautiful or so unique.
它让你非常非常印象深刻，因为它太美或太独特了。
Okay, so for example, the views, the view of the beach is stunning, right?
好的，比如，景色，海滩的景色是绝美的，对吧？
Or even someone, you can say, wow, you look stunning.
或者甚至形容一个人，你可以说，哇，你看起来绝美。
That's right.
没错。
So this is a really great compliment, by the way.
所以顺便说一句，这是一个非常好的赞美。
Usually men say this to women.
通常男人对女人这么说。
Women don't say this to men.
女人不对男人这么说。
You can describe someone's clothes as stunning, like her dress was stunning at the Oscars.
你可以形容一个人的衣服是绝美的，比如她在奥斯卡上的裙子是绝美的。
But if you're a man trying to give a woman a good compliment, believe me, this one works.
但如果你是一个男人想给女人一个好的赞美，相信我，这个很管用。
You look stunning this evening.
你今晚看起来绝美。
Okay, nice little tip there.
好的，一个小提示。
Using the adjective stunning.
使用形容词“绝美”。
Okay, now lush.
好的，现在说“郁郁葱葱”。
We have lush green gardens.
我们有郁郁葱葱的绿色花园。
So we're looking, we have a stunning view of the lush green gardens.
所以我们看到，我们有郁郁葱葱的绿色花园的绝美景色。
This word lush.
这个词“郁郁葱葱”。
Lush usually describes things that are organic, like plants and flowers.
“郁郁葱葱”通常形容有机的东西，比如植物和花。
And we say this to mean that something is very green, very healthy, very full.
我们这么说意味着某物非常绿、非常健康、非常茂盛。
Okay, so an apple tree, full with apples and you have a, it just looks great.
好的，比如一棵苹果树，挂满了苹果，看起来很棒。
You would say it's a lush apple tree.
你会说这是一棵郁郁葱葱的苹果树。
Right, or I could even say, I've heard that the rainforests of Ecuador are very, very
对，或者我甚至可以说，我听说厄瓜多尔的雨林非常非常
lush, very green.
郁郁葱葱，非常绿。
Yeah, exactly.
是的，没错。
All right, so lush, they're very abundant, very green, very healthy.
好的，所以“郁郁葱葱”，它们非常丰富、非常绿、非常健康。
And apart from these adjectives, the sales agent also described that the country villa
除了这些形容词，销售代理还描述了这家乡村别墅
had recently been restored and refurbished.
最近被修复和翻新过。
So what about these two words, restored and refurbished?
那么这两个词“修复”和“翻新”是什么意思呢？
Okay, basically what she's saying is that this house, this big villa, was recently completely
好的，基本上她说的是这栋房子，这个大别墅，最近内部完全
remade on the inside.
重新改造了。
So the appearance, the look doesn't really change.
所以外观、样子没有太大变化。
It's still an old, beautiful villa, but maybe the insides were old or needed to be updated.
它仍然是一个古老、美丽的别墅，但也许内部老旧了或需要更新。
And so that means that the plumbing, the lights, the walls, the paint, that was all restored,
所以这意味着管道、灯、墙壁、油漆，都被修复了，
maybe to look like the original, very, very beautiful and clean.
也许是为了看起来像原来的样子，非常非常漂亮和干净。
But also it was refurbished, which means that the fittings and the carpet and maybe the
但同时也被翻新了，这意味着配件、地毯，也许还有
lights and all the furniture, that was also new again.
灯和所有家具，也都是新的了。
Okay, so we usually hear about this sometimes in the news when they are restoring an old
好的，所以我们通常在新闻里听到这个，当他们修复一座古老的
church or an old building.
教堂或古老建筑时。
That means they're making it, they're trying to save it and make it look like it used to.
这意味着他们正在努力保存它，让它看起来像以前的样子。
They're not changing it, right?
他们没有改变它，对吧？
They're not trying to make it look new, but they're trying to make it look like it used
他们不是想让它看起来新，而是想让它看起来像
to look before it got old.
变旧之前的样子。
You know how sometimes old things are worn and they're not pretty anymore?
你知道有时候旧东西会磨损，不再好看吗？
Well, what they're trying to do is make it really shiny and beautiful.
嗯，他们想做的就是让它变得闪亮又漂亮。
And refurbish is basically to give it, as you said, new carpet or sometimes new furniture
而翻新基本上就是给它，就像你说的，换新地毯或者有时候换新家具，
or stuff like that.
或者类似的东西。
So many people refurbish their homes, right?
很多人都会翻新自己的家，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
And it's a very, very popular thing to do with older houses.
而且这对老房子来说是非常非常流行的事情。
You buy them, you fix them, you restore them, you refurbish them so that you want to live
你买下它们，修理它们，恢复它们，翻新它们，这样你就想住在
in them.
里面。
Right.
对。
Okay.
好的。
So a lot of great things from this dialogue.
这段对话里有很多很棒的内容。
I think we should listen to it one more time and we'll be back in a little bit.
我觉得我们应该再听一遍，然后一会儿回来。
Welcome to Perfect Getaway Tours.
欢迎来到完美度假之旅。
How can I help you?
有什么可以帮您的吗？
I would like to plan a surprise getaway for me and my wife.
我想为我和我妻子计划一个惊喜度假。
Very well.
很好。
We have a couple of different options such as beaches, the wilderness, the countryside,
我们有几种不同的选择，比如海滩、荒野、乡村，
or even going to a spa for the weekend.
或者甚至周末去水疗中心。
I think something in the countryside would be nice.
我觉得乡村的某个地方会不错。
Perfect.
完美。
This package includes round trip flights to New Hampshire.
这个套餐包括往返新罕布什尔州的航班。
A free airport pickup is included.
包含免费机场接送。
Our VIP limousine will pick you up and provide you with complimentary champagne and finger
我们的VIP豪华轿车会接您，并提供免费香槟和小吃，
foods to soften the 30 minute ride to the countryside.
让30分钟的车程到乡村更轻松。
Sounds good.
听起来不错。
What is the hotel that we'll be staying at like?
我们要住的酒店是什么样的？
That is the best part.
那是最棒的部分。
Your hotel is actually an old country villa that has been restored and refurbished to
您的酒店实际上是一座经过修复和翻新的古老乡村别墅，
accommodate a maximum of 10 guests.
最多可容纳10位客人。
You will enjoy an intimate and private time in this very spacious and warm hotel.
您将在这个非常宽敞温馨的酒店里享受私密而安静的时光。
Included in the price is three meals a day, excluding beverages.
价格包含一日三餐，不包括饮料。
You can choose to eat at the fabulous restaurant that offers a stunning view of the lush green
您可以选择在提供壮丽翠绿花园景色的
gardens.
绝佳餐厅用餐。
Or if you prefer, your own private butler can arrange your meal to be served in your
或者如果您愿意，您的私人管家可以安排餐点送到您的
room or outside on our terrace.
房间或外面的露台上。
Wow, this sounds like something my wife would really enjoy.
哇，这听起来像我妻子会非常喜欢的东西。
Are there any outdoor activities we can take part in?
有什么户外活动可以参加吗？
Of course.
当然。
The hotel has a stable with beautiful stallions for a very romantic horseback ride along the
酒店有一个马厩，里面有漂亮的公马，可以沿着乡村小径
country trail.
进行非常浪漫的骑马之旅。
You can also go fishing at the nearby lake or visit the local vineyard.
您还可以在附近的湖边钓鱼或参观当地的葡萄园。
I'm sold.
我决定了。
I want to book this trip.
我想预订这次旅行。
I don't care what it costs.
我不在乎花多少钱。
Money is no object.
钱不是问题。
All right, so talking about getaways.
好了，那么说到度假。
Now the sales agent offered him options such as beach, wilderness, countryside, or even
现在销售代理给了他一些选择，比如海滩、荒野、乡村，甚至
a spa.
水疗中心。
Which one do you prefer?
你更喜欢哪一个？
Wilderness.
荒野。
For sure.
毫无疑问。
You want to go into the forest, the jungle.
你想去森林、丛林里。
Yes, I hate to say it.
是的，我虽然不想这么说。
I think beaches are boring.
我觉得海滩很无聊。
Sorry, mom.
对不起，妈妈。
I know you love beaches.
我知道你喜欢海滩。
I like to do stuff when I'm away.
我外出时喜欢做点事情。
I love the desert too, but the wilderness, somewhere where I'm outside.
我也喜欢沙漠，但荒野，那种户外的感觉。
I live in a city.
我住在城市里。
I don't want to go to a city.
我不想去另一个城市。
I like to go somewhere where I can walk around, hike, ride a bike, do things like that.
我喜欢去可以散步、徒步、骑自行车之类的地方。
What about you?
你呢？
I actually don't have a favorite, actually.
我其实没有特别喜欢的。
Sometimes it's nice for me to go to the beach and relax.
有时候去海滩放松一下也不错。
I do tend to get a little bit bored after maybe two days of doing nothing on the beach.
在海滩上无所事事两天后，我确实会有点无聊。
But it does give a good opportunity to do other things, beach activities like snorkeling
但它也提供了做其他事情的好机会，比如海滩活动，像浮潜
or scuba diving, which can also be really fun.
或水肺潜水，这些也很有趣。
But definitely I do enjoy the wilderness as well, the jungle and rafting or camping.
但当然我也喜欢荒野，丛林、漂流或露营。
It's good fun.
很好玩。
The insects can be a bit of a nuisance at times.
昆虫有时候会有点烦人。
Or the rain.
或者下雨。
Getting in the snow or the rain is so horrible.
遇到雪或雨真是太糟糕了。
But other than that, yeah, it's great.
但除此之外，是的，很棒。
I know not many people enjoy these types of outdoor getaways.
我知道不是很多人喜欢这种类型的户外度假。
But of course, you have spas.
但当然，还有水疗中心。
I know many people enjoy going to a spa, having a mud bath.
我知道很多人喜欢去水疗中心，做泥浴。
Nothing wrong with that.
这没什么不好。
Getting your nails done, having a massage.
做指甲、按摩。
Getting the whole royal treatment, like we say.
享受全套皇家待遇，就像我们常说的那样。
So this is what we want to know now.
所以这就是我们现在想知道的。
When you go on vacation, what do you like to do?
你去度假时，喜欢做什么？
Do you like to get away to the tropical beaches?
你喜欢去热带海滩放松吗？
Do you like to go to the islands or the jungle?
你喜欢去岛屿还是丛林？
What do you like to do?
你喜欢做什么？
Let us know.
告诉我们吧。
Our website is EnglishPod.com.
我们的网站是 EnglishPod.com。
We hope to see you there.
我们希望能在那儿见到你。
All right.
好了。
We'll see you guys next time.
我们下次再见。
Bye.
拜拜。
Please subscibe to EnglandAndTheWest.com
请订阅 EnglandAndTheWest.com。